they say Society plays an important role
in our lives it shapes our culture and
makes us the individuals we are today
but when Society begins to stereotype us
is when life begins to get
[Music]
difficult lady driver a
bus K banana is always going to be a
women's
job it's okay for him he's a boy men
don't cry
wom women should not be out
late men should earn more wom
are ICI Lombard presents all okay please
a celebration of our diversity equity
and
inclusion come witness the Journey of
our champions from ICICI Lombard who
went beyond the tide to break every
barrier and every
[Music]
stereotype when I was 12 I got behind
the wheel on slide and convinced my
father's driver to teach me driving and
3 days later I was in perfect control
today I'm a national level racer and I
have won close to 32 events including
many events where I have been the
fastest women driver well I'm asked
which is the most hair raising event of
your life there are many but I will
quote one in extreme racism mealia my
car toppled at a hair pin bent at a very
very high speed and crashed it caught
fire and I was pulled out but here I am
in front of you it's definitely not easy
being a woman driver in male dominated
sport-like Motorsports racing in most of
the off-roading events I still find
myself as the only female driver among
loads of male
participants internet lady
drivers but next time whenever you make
any judgment on a women driver think of
me
from the time I can remember I've always
been a foodie but I cook pretty rarely
maybe once or twice a month at the most
but lockdown T I became the designated
chef of the house throughout the
lockdown and trust me I loved it YouTube
recipes zindabad but now I began
experimenting with traditional recipes I
specialize in all kinds of Cuisine North
Indian South Indian Chinese Thai Italian
French sub
and while I experiment I'm also a purist
in cooking I love to prepare everything
right from scratch from the BSA batter
to the pizza base now that we are back
to working from office I indulge in my
passion mainly on weekends but if you
still think cooking is only a woman's
job all I can say is you've got to
change your
[Music]
thinking I started weight training just
3 years back and before I knew it I was
drawn to weightlifting as a sport my
fitness coach is a professional Olympic
weightlifter he pushed me to participate
at a district level competition and
journey
start I was hesitant and honestly very
intimidated for adrenaline Rashana it
overpowers all negative thoughts waking
up at 5:00 a.m. intense training for 3
hours followed by a 2-hour commute to
work is not everybody's cup of tea
but weightlifting has taught me how to
remain confident in the face of any
adversity I'm a proper mumbay car from
shivaji Park kite flying is very popular
here seeing colorful kites in the sky
was a great sight and flying it seems to
be great fun but a problem the only boys
were flying kite and at the most my
brothers allowed me to hold a chakri and
had all the fun
why should boys have all the fun and I
resorted to typical Bombay jugar I
started waking up early much earlier
than my brothers and started training
myself to fly a kite P to I think it was
little tough I didn't know how to select
the right kite how to tie
but in the morning one day after four
five attempts my kite flew high and
thereafter no looking back it was so
liberating it was thrilling
[Music]
I have been a classical dancer since I
was
13 Indian classical dance requires you
to be in a touch with your feminine as
well as a masculine site
imagine side effects at first my friends
used to make fun of me but I got used to
it at is Lombard I feel at
home in fact in talent show organized
for our Founders Day I was selected to
do my classical dance and got another
chance to pursue my
[Music]
passion my Fascination for riding
started early college I used to see the
boys riding these heavy fancy bikes and
I always thought why not me biking is
difficult for women bike
ladies but I just wanted to challenge
these
thoughts
[Music]
I bought my first bike in 2006 since
then I have ridden to ladak Shri nagar
Manali spiti and many other circuits on
my way back from one of my Manali rides
recently I was badly stuck in a
landslide in spite of knowing that I
won't be able to join work the next day
my supervisor was worried about my
safety he assured me that he will manage
my work till I am back either office May
everyone respects my passion and lets me
be
[Music]
me my goal in life is to prove these
people wrong that's why I chose mixed
martial art and kickboxing I'm a
national level kickboxer State and
District level gold medalist you may not
believe it but I can fight men and women
of any age
gr women are not
weak family
or Office business or
passion every woman should be called a
[Music]
superwoman at icic Lombard we don't
stereotype anyone we don't label anyone
we don't restrict
anyone because at ICICI Lombard we
believe that you do your best only when
you are the best version of your
[Music]
s